<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pochi</title>
    <link>https://tamada.github.io/pochi/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pochi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 11:19:09 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tamada.github.io/pochi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Description</title>
      <link>https://tamada.github.io/pochi/description/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tamada.github.io/pochi/description/</guid>
      <description>Key idea Almost traditional birthmark systems are usually simple input and output. For example, an user specifies the type of target birthmark, $p$ and $q$ as input, and obtains result as output. The process of such system is hard to use. Because, when the user would perform some process (ex. filtering results), it requires the update of birthmark system.
In general, the process of birthmarking is composed of extraction phase, and comparison phase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birthmarks</title>
      <link>https://tamada.github.io/pochi/birthmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tamada.github.io/pochi/birthmarks/</guid>
      <description>Definition of Birthmarks Types of Birthmarks Similarities Theft Detection Process by Birthmarks  Definition of Birthmarks Let $p$, and $q$ be a given programs, and $\mathcal{B}_f(p)$ be set of characteristics extracted from $p$ by a given method $f$. If the conditions below are met, $\mathcal{B}_f(p)$ is said to be a birthmark of $p$.
 Condition 1: $\mathcal{B}_f(p)$ is obtained from only program $p$. Condition 2: If $q$ is a copy of $p$, then $\mathcal{B}_f(p) = \mathcal{B}_f(q)$.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://tamada.github.io/pochi/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tamada.github.io/pochi/about/</guid>
      <description>License Apache License version 2.0
Apache License, version 2.0.
Copyright 2017, Haruaki Tamada.
Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &amp;quot;License&amp;quot;); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0  Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an &amp;quot;AS IS&amp;quot; BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview（概要）</title>
      <link>https://tamada.github.io/pochi/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tamada.github.io/pochi/overview/</guid>
      <description>Overview This product is the software birthmark platform for Java programs. The software birthmark aims to detect the theft of programs from characteristics of the programs.
Typical scenario of the birthmarking is:
 to extract birthmarks of the specified type from programs, to compare extracted birthmarks, and compute similarities among birthmarks, and to detect similar programs from the computed similarities.  Note that birthmarks do not prove the theft, just detect suspected theft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install</title>
      <link>https://tamada.github.io/pochi/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tamada.github.io/pochi/install/</guid>
      <description>Homebrew For macOS user, pochi supports homebrew installation.
$ brew tap tamada/brew $ brew install pochi   Go totop of the page
Compiling pochi yourself For building yourself, clone the source code from GitHub, and build it with Maven.
$ git clone https://github.com/tamada/pochi.git $ cd pochi $ mvn package  Then, maven packages pochi and generates pochi-1.0.0-fat.jar, and pochi-1.0.0-all.jar onto distribution/target directory.
 Go totop of the page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Usage</title>
      <link>https://tamada.github.io/pochi/usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tamada.github.io/pochi/usage/</guid>
      <description>CLI Interface $ pochi [OPTIONS] [SCRIPT [ARGV...]] OPTIONS: -e &amp;lt;EXPRESSION&amp;gt; one line of script. -config &amp;lt;CONFIG&amp;gt; specify the configuration file. -help print this message and exit. -version print the version. -license print the license. SCRIPT [ARGV...] Specify the script file for executing. Suitable script engine is parsed from extension of the script file. ARGV is arguments list for the script. NO SCRIPT FILE, and NO ONE LINER If no script file and no one liner were specified, pochi runs on interactive mode.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>